is AI good at selling to us shit if if you can convince a 57 year old to enjoy tiktok shopping
yeah i bought some things off tiktok shop and i haven't been displeased yet and i would have told
you that that's stupid i'd never do that i'm all into tiktok shop but all right so ChatGPT ads
yeah is AI a good salesperson yes better than a human absolutely a human at any level sure let's
go for that and that's what's going to happen be careful hide your credit card don't give it up
right away if you track back to when i was younger and people were to say hey have you bought anything
online yet? I remember that conversation. Have you bought anything? Well. no. I don't think I
even had a credit card then. but it would have been. no. I haven't bought anything online. Oh.
you got to try it. It's so easy. It's so wonderful. Well. aren't you worried about somebody getting
your credit card information or somebody stealing all the money out of your account or whatever?
Well. yeah. it kind of bothered me for a little bit. but nothing happened. And lo and behold.